Hello, it's a
very good jam, it's a killer,
in the next video, till then goodbye,
hello friends, welcome to back staff, friends,
last year it was 19600 41, so you can say that the
expenses have increased a bit and the quarter end
and the quarter underwater are also very good, the
quarter is also showing a slight increase, the
result of this serial Tech water for has come, we are
seeing a growth, if it is of the company
that year after year there is a good jump and it is
not a matter of expenses being big, so what has happened
here, first of all you should see 18,
good things, last year's
quarter water is also seeing a slight increase, the
income has also increased, using the increase in income, by
declaring interim dividend, it is
getting a very good profit in comparison, if we add other income to it and
cover a little expenses, it is a natural thing, the
company has given and which is its recorded
time and this quarter compared to the previous quarter,
now the profit of the company is written here, if we look at it, then
this time there has been a
good increase in the total of HCL Tech, even if it is a slight
Look here, 29th April, that is,
look at it, but this before tax, that is, the
income will be
big, but it has increased, now here on the
28th, if you
look at the EPS of the company, which is 22954, which is the previous quarter before paying tax and after spending, which is different this time, then on the
27th, inside this
water three, it was 22500 86 and
what is left in the hands of the company last year is 4320, 3
points 276 1269 and the previous part will have to be
bought, the shares of Serial Tech, here
in the quarter form, it was 19800 500 or so
in the previous quarter it was 4438 and
one more thing is written on the previous year, look, I
was four points advanced year after year,
payment was also given within a black, the
income of the company has been completed for a good year and
in the quarter four it was 3367, but it will go now,
this is the date of payment, let's move on to
quarter underwater in both  This increase
quarter by quarter, we are
seeing here, it is a good thing, now if
you can see one thing on the company's results here,
let's say the company's income has been the
main pocket of the company, now in this the
profit of the company will increase, so you can see this also
after the tax is adjusted,
you will see the number here in crores, it is
very good, the company's profit will
increase a bit, it is a good thing, so friends, you will get
to see it, now let me
also take a look at the child's war in the hands of the company, I will
adjust the list of the company's express given here so that it is clear, the
net profit of the company here, this is
according to the company, hence the result of take water for, if
you want, all three quarters were
very good, you have the Yagya share,
this is the number of this time and this is the last time the
net profit is written, you can do the profit for the
one by one, we will take
it for a while in the period,
so you can hole it with an alarm, so this is the
number of quarter three and this is the last year, we would have
completed only the total express
so that you can understand clearly,
then that's it for now  Information if the
quota for number is given here
which this time is the total of HCL Tech you must have
liked this video
3599 Net profit of HCL Tech which
we start here with Ravindra Operation
Expense 18,000 593 last time it was 18,000 please give it a like
and if you are new to this channel then let's do it
which this time is 22500 97 and
in the previous quarter it was 3448 and last year
subscribe to the channel because the share was
156 and last year in the quarter for we get
market related updates on this channel in the
quarter for 1111 hey friend hey friend
in the last quarter it was 22 thousand so 31 which we keep
bringing at last we get
16000 pass quota 18 year after year of the company
[Music]